Guide to the Time Inc. Time Research Center Files: Subject Files MS 3009-RG 13.Series III
New-York Historical Society
- Series III. Subject Files, 1926-2000; 774 Linear feet (774 boxes)
  - Wars: World War II: Reparations: From United States, 1963-1990 (Offsite-box 2704, Folder 22)
  - Wars: World War II: Reparations: From United States: To Philippines, 1962-1964 (Offsite-box 2704, Folder 23)
  - Wars: World War II: Reparations: To A-Z, 1956-1989 (Offsite-box 2704, Folder 24)
  - Wars: World War II: Strategy, 1939-1990 (Offsite-box 2704, Folder 25)
  - Wars: World War II: Strategy: Air, 1941-1942 (Offsite-box 2704, Folder 26)
  - Wars: World War II: Strategy: Axis, 1941-1989 (Offsite-box 2704, Folder 27)
  - Wars: World War II: Strategy: By France, 1955 (Offsite-box 2704, Folder 28)
  - Wars: World War II: Strategy: By Germany, 1942-1990 (Offsite-box 2704, Folder 29)
  - Wars: World War II: Strategy: By Germany: Navy, 1942 (Offsite-box 2704, Folder 30)
  - Wars: World War II: Strategy: By Germany: Navy: Submarine, 1943-1962 (Offsite-box 2704, Folder 31)
  - Wars: World War II: Strategy: By Great Britain, 1942-1993 (Offsite-box 2704, Folder 32)
  - Wars: World War II: Strategy: By Great Britain: Air, 1941-1961 (Offsite-box 2704, Folder 33)
  - Wars: World War II: Strategy: By Great Britain: Army, 1939 (Offsite-box 2704, Folder 34)
  - Wars: World War II: Strategy: By Great Britain: Navy, 1940 (Offsite-box 2704, Folder 35)
  - Wars: World War II: Strategy: By Japan, 1942-1991 (Offsite-box 2704, Folder 36)
  - Wars: World War II: Strategy: By Japan: Navy, 1944 (Offsite-box 2705, Folder 1)
  - Wars: World War II: Strategy: By Union of Soviet Socialist Republics, 1942-1987 (Offsite-box 2705, Folder 2)
  - Wars: World War II: Strategy: By United Nations, 1942-1959 (Offsite-box 2705, Folder 3)
  - Wars: World War II: Strategy: By United Nations: Air, 1943 (Offsite-box 2705, Folder 4)
  - Wars: World War II: Strategy: By United States, 1948-1993 (Offsite-box 2705, Folder 5)
  - Wars: World War II: Strategy: By United States: Air, 1941-1990 (Offsite-box 2705, Folder 6-7)
  - Wars: World War II: Strategy: By United States: Army, 1943-1956 (Offsite-box 2705, Folder 8)
  - Wars: World War II: Strategy: By United States: Navy, 1941-1942 (Offsite-box 2705, Folder 9)
  - Wars: World War II: Strategy: Comparison with other wars, 1961-1969 (Offsite-box 2705, Folder 10)
  - Wars: World War II: Strategy: In Africa, 1942 (Offsite-box 2705, Folder 11)
  - Wars: World War II: Strategy: In Belgium, 1969 (Offsite-box 2705, Folder 12)
  - Wars: World War II: Strategy: In Belgium and Netherlands, 1939-1941 (Offsite-box 2705, Folder 13)
  - Wars: World War II: Strategy: In China, 1942-1955 (Offsite-box 2705, Folder 14)
  - Wars: World War II: Strategy: In Denmark, 1961 (Offsite-box 2705, Folder 15)
  - Wars: World War II: Strategy: In East, Far, 1943-1946 (Offsite-box 2705, Folder 16)
  - Wars: World War II: Strategy: In East, Near, 1942 (Offsite-box 2705, Folder 17)
  - Wars: World War II: Strategy: In Europe, 1961 (Offsite-box 2705, Folder 18)
  - Wars: World War II: Strategy: In Europe: By Germany, 1940 (Offsite-box 2705, Folder 19)
  - Wars: World War II: Strategy: In Europe: By Great Britain, 1944-1945 (Offsite-box 2705, Folder 20)
  - Wars: World War II: Strategy: In Europe: By United Nations, 1943-1944 (Offsite-box 2705, Folder 21)
  - Wars: World War II: Strategy: In Europe: By United Nations: Air, 1943-1944 (Offsite-box 2705, Folder 22)
  - Wars: World War II: Strategy: In Finland, 1940 (Offsite-box 2705, Folder 23)
  - Wars: World War II: Strategy: In France, 1944-1984 (Offsite-box 2705, Folder 24)
  - Wars: World War II: Strategy: In Germany, 1959-1961 (Offsite-box 2705, Folder 25)
  - Wars: World War II: Strategy: In Great Britain, 1942-1961 (Offsite-box 2705, Folder 26)
  - Wars: World War II: Strategy: In Italy: By United Nations, 1944-1966 (Offsite-box 2705, Folder 27)
  - Wars: World War II: Strategy: In Japan, 1945-1955 (Offsite-box 2705, Folder 28)
  - Wars: World War II: Strategy: In Libya, 1941 (Offsite-box 2705, Folder 29)
  - Wars: World War II: Strategy: In Malaya, 1942 (Offsite-box 2705, Folder 30)
  - Wars: World War II: Strategy: In Mediterranean, 1943 (Offsite-box 2705, Folder 31)
  - Wars: World War II: Strategy: In Norway, 1940-1958 (Offsite-box 2705, Folder 32)
  - Wars: World War II: Strategy: In Pacific, 1991 (Offsite-box 2705, Folder 33)
  - Wars: World War II: Strategy: In Pacific: By Great Britain [Empty], Undated (Offsite-box 2705, Folder 34)
  - Wars: World War II: Strategy: In Pacific: By Japan, 1943-1966 (Offsite-box 2705, Folder 35)
  - Wars: World War II: Strategy: In Pacific: By United Nations, 1943-1944 (Offsite-box 2705, Folder 36)
  - Wars: World War II: Strategy: In Pacific: By United States, 1942-1985 (Offsite-box 2705, Folder 37)
  - Wars: World War II: Strategy: In Pacific: By United States: Air, 1943-1944 (Offsite-box 2705, Folder 38)
  - Wars: World War II: Strategy: In Pacific: By United States: Navy, 1940-1944 (Offsite-box 2705, Folder 39)
  - Wars: World War II: Strategy: In Philippines: By Japan, 1945 (Offsite-box 2705, Folder 40)
  - Wars: World War II: Strategy: In Philippines: By United States, 1941-1992 (Offsite-box 2705, Folder 41)
  - Wars: World War II: Strategy: In Poland, 1939-1964 (Offsite-box 2705, Folder 42)
  - Wars: World War II: Strategy: In Sicily, 1943-1985 (Offsite-box 2706, Folder 1)
  - Wars: World War II: Strategy: In Singapore, 1941 (Offsite-box 2706, Folder 2)
  - Wars: World War II: Strategy: In Switzerland: By Germany, 1950 (Offsite-box 2706, Folder 3)
  - Wars: World War II: Strategy: In Tunisia, 1943 (Offsite-box 2706, Folder 4)
  - Wars: World War II: Strategy: In Turkey, 1942 (Offsite-box 2706, Folder 5)
  - Wars: World War II: Strategy: In Union of Soviet Socialist Republics: By Germany, 1941-1945 (Offsite-box 2706, Folder 6)
  - Wars: World War II: Strategy: In Union of Soviet Socialist Republics: By Union of Soviet Socialist Republics, 1941-1969 (Offsite-box 2706, Folder 7)
  - Wars: World War II: Strategy: In United States: By Axis, 1940-1975 (Offsite-box 2706, Folder 8)
  - Wars: World War II: Strategy: In United States: By Germany, 1990 (Offsite-box 2706, Folder 9)
  - Wars: World War II: Strategy: Navy, 1940-1964 (Offsite-box 2706, Folder 10)
  - Wars: World War II: Surveys, 1939-1993 (Offsite-box 2706, Folder 11-12)
  - Wars: World War II: Termination, 1965-1990 (Offsite-box 2706, Folder 13)
  - Wars: World War II: Truces, 1944-1975 (Offsite-box 2706, Folder 14)
  - Wars: World War II: War Criminals, 1970-1993 (Offsite-box 2706, Folder 15-20)
  - Wars: World War II: War Criminals: A-Z, 1945-1993 (Offsite-box 2706, Folder 21)
  - Wars: World War II: War Criminals: Austria, 1975-1988 (Offsite-box 2706, Folder 22)
  - Wars: World War II: War Criminals: Balkans, 1987-1991 (Offsite-box 2706, Folder 23-25)
  - Wars: World War II: War criminals: Balkans, 1986 (Offsite-box 2707, Folder 1)
  - Wars: World War II: War criminals: Belgium, 1962-1990 (Offsite-box 2707, Folder 2)
  - Wars: World War II: War criminals: Estonia, 1961-1987 (Offsite-box 2707, Folder 3)
  - Wars: World War II: War criminals: Europe, 1977-1991 (Offsite-box 2707, Folder 4)
  - Wars: World War II: War criminals: France, 1952-1993 (Offsite-box 2707, Folder 5-9)
  - Wars: World War II: War criminals: Germany, 1967-1993 (Offsite-box 2707, Folder 10-30)
  - Wars: World War II: War criminals: Germany, 1942-1959 (Offsite-box 2708, Folder 1-8)
  - Wars: World War II: War criminals: Germany: Associations, 1972-1985 (Offsite-box 2708, Folder 9)
  - Wars: World War II: War criminals: Germany: Asylum, 1972-1985 (Offsite-box 2708, Folder 10)
  - Wars: World War II: War criminals: Germany: Trials, 1951-1992 (Offsite-box 2708, Folder 11-13)
  - Wars: World War II: War criminals: Germany: Trials: A, 1945-1972 (Offsite-box 2708, Folder 14)
  - Wars: World War II: War criminals: Germany: Trials: B, 1964-1969 (Offsite-box 2708, Folder 15)
  - Wars: World War II: War criminals: Germany: Trials: Berlin, 1961-1992 (Offsite-box 2708, Folder 16)
  - Wars: World War II: War criminals: Germany: Trials: Bonn, 1962-1979 (Offsite-box 2708, Folder 17)
  - Wars: World War II: War criminals: Germany: Trials: Bordeaux, 1953 (Offsite-box 2708, Folder 18)
  - Wars: World War II: War criminals: Germany: Trials: C, 1964-1980 (Offsite-box 2708, Folder 19)
  - Wars: World War II: War criminals: Germany: Trials: D, 1946-1981 (Offsite-box 2708, Folder 20)
  - Wars: World War II: War criminals: Germany: Trials: Dachau, 1947-1985 (Offsite-box 2708, Folder 21)
  - Wars: World War II: War criminals: Germany: Trials: E, 1965-1969 (Offsite-box 2708, Folder 22)
  - Wars: World War II: War criminals: Germany: Trials: F, 1962-1982 (Offsite-box 2708, Folder 23)
  - Wars: World War II: War criminals: Germany: Trials: Frankfurt, 1964-1966 (Offsite-box 2708, Folder 24)
  - Wars: World War II: War criminals: Germany: Trials: G, 1964-1986 (Offsite-box 2708, Folder 25)
  - Wars: World War II: War criminals: Germany: Trials: H, 1963-1977 (Offsite-box 2708, Folder 26)
  - Wars: World War II: War criminals: Germany: Trials: Jerusalem, 1961-1966 (Offsite-box 2708, Folder 27-32)
  - Wars: World War II: War criminals: Germany: Trials: Jerusalem, 1961 (Offsite-box 2709, Folder 1-3)
  - Wars: World War II: War criminals: Germany: Trials: K, 1944-1981 (Offsite-box 2709, Folder 4)
  - Wars: World War II: War criminals: Germany: Trials: Koblenz, 1963 (Offsite-box 2709, Folder 5)
  - Wars: World War II: War criminals: Germany: Trials: L, 1945-1993 (Offsite-box 2709, Folder 6)
  - Wars: World War II: War criminals: Germany: Trials: Limburg, 1964-1975 (Offsite-box 2709, Folder 7)
  - Wars: World War II: War criminals: Germany: Trials: M, 1946-1968 (Offsite-box 2709, Folder 8)
  - Wars: World War II: War criminals: Germany: Trials: Munich, 1964-1967 (Offsite-box 2709, Folder 9)
  - Wars: World War II: War criminals: Germany: Trials: Nuremberg, 1945-1992 (Offsite-box 2709, Folder 10-14)
  - Wars: World War II: War criminals: Germany: Trials: O, 1965 (Offsite-box 2709, Folder 15)
  - Wars: World War II: War criminals: Germany: Trials: P, 1949 (Offsite-box 2709, Folder 16)
  - Wars: World War II: War criminals: Germany: Trials: R, 1945-1948 (Offsite-box 2709, Folder 17)
  - Wars: World War II: War criminals: Germany: Trials: S, 1961-1991 (Offsite-box 2709, Folder 18)
  - Wars: World War II: War criminals: Germany: Trials: T, 1961-1979 (Offsite-box 2709, Folder 19)
  - Wars: World War II: War criminals: Germany: Trials: U, 1958-1964 (Offsite-box 2709, Folder 20)
  - Wars: World War II: War criminals: Germany: Trials: V, 1964-1972 (Offsite-box 2709, Folder 21)
  - Wars: World War II: War criminals: Germany: Trials: W, 1947-1968 (Offsite-box 2709, Folder 22)
  - Wars: World War II: War criminals: Greece, 1986-1989 (Offsite-box 2709, Folder 23)
  - Wars: World War II: War criminals: Hungary, 1955-1992 (Offsite-box 2709, Folder 24)
  - Wars: World War II: War criminals: Israel, 1992-1993 (Offsite-box 2709, Folder 25)
  - Wars: World War II: War criminals: Italy, 1985-1988 (Offsite-box 2709, Folder 26)
  - Wars: World War II: War criminals: Japan, 1956-1993 (Offsite-box 2709, Folder 27)
  - Wars: World War II: War criminals: Japan: Trials: A-Z, 1964-1984 (Offsite-box 2709, Folder 28)
  - Wars: World War II: War criminals: Japan: Trials: Manila, 1945-1974 (Offsite-box 2709, Folder 29)
  - Wars: World War II: War criminals: Japan: Trials: Tokyo, 1945-1987 (Offsite-box 2709, Folder 30)
  - Wars: World War II: War criminals: Japan: Yokohama, 1948-1949 (Offsite-box 2710, Folder 1)
  - Wars: World War II: War criminals: Latvia, 1977-1988 (Offsite-box 2710, Folder 2)
  - Wars: World War II: War criminals: Lithuania, 1978-1993 (Offsite-box 2710, Folder 3)
  - Wars: World War II: War criminals: Netherlands, 1961-1991 (Offsite-box 2710, Folder 4)
  - Wars: World War II: War criminals: Poland, 1955-1993 (Offsite-box 2710, Folder 5-8)
  - Wars: World War II: War criminals: Rumania, 1955-1991 (Offsite-box 2710, Folder 9)
  - Wars: World War II: War criminals: Union of Soviet Socialist Republics, 1968-1991 (Offsite-box 2710, Folder 10)
  - Wars: World War II: War criminals: Yugoslavia, 1951-1993 (Offsite-box 2710, Folder 11-12)
  - Wars: World War II: Works about, 1979-1993 (Offsite-box 2710, Folder 13-14)
  - Women: Europe, 1950-1973 (Offsite-box 2710, Folder 15)
  - Women: Germany, 1934-1993 (Offsite-box 2710, Folder 16-20)
  - Wool: United States, 1934-1960 (Offsite-box 2710, Folder 21-22)
  - Words and phrases, 1960-1991 (Offsite-box 2711, Folder 1-5)
  - Words and phrases: A-At, 1931-1993 (Offsite-box 2711, Folder 6-22)
  - Words and phrases: Au-Az, 1940-1989 (Offsite-box 2712, Folder 1)
  - Words and phrases: Abbreviations, 1934-1991 (Offsite-box 2712, Folder 2-5)
  - Words and phrases: Afro-American, 1968-1991 (Offsite-box 2712, Folder 6)
  - Words and phrases: Associations, 1964-1982 (Offsite-box 2712, Folder 7)
  - Words and phrases: Baa-Blz, 1939-1993 (Offsite-box 2712, Folder 8-25)
  - Words and phrases: Bm-Bz, 1935-1992 (Offsite-box 2713, Folder 1-9)
  - Words and phrases: Beatlemania, 1963-1964 (Offsite-box 2713, Folder 10)
  - Words and phrases: Benign neglect, 1970-1976 (Offsite-box 2713, Folder 11)
  - Words and phrases: Big Apple, 1975-1990 (Offsite-box 2713, Folder 12)
  - Words and phrases: Black is Beautiful, 1967-1974 (Offsite-box 2713, Folder 13)
  - Words and phrases: Boondoggle, 1937-1982 (Offsite-box 2713, Folder 14)
  - Words and phrases: Brainwashing, 1967-1976 (Offsite-box 2713, Folder 15)
  - Words and phrases: Caa-Chh, 1932-1993 (Offsite-box 2713, Folder 16-25)
  - Words and phrases: Chi-Cz, 1935-1993 (Offsite-box 2714, Folder 1-16)
  - Words and phrases: Carpetbag, 1934-1988 (Offsite-box 2714, Folder 17)
  - Words and phrases: Cept, 1965 (Offsite-box 2714, Folder 18)
  - Words and phrases: Cliches, 1958-1992 (Offsite-box 2714, Folder 19)
  - Words and phrases: Cold War, 1947-1992 (Offsite-box 2714, Folder 20)
  - Words and phrases: Collective nouns, 1951-1985 (Offsite-box 2715, Folder 1)
  - Words and phrases: Creativity, 1957-1960 (Offsite-box 2715, Folder 2)
  - Words and phrases: Credibility, 1961-1970 (Offsite-box 2715, Folder 3)
  - Words and phrases: Credibility gap, 1962-1970 (Offsite-box 2715, Folder 4)
  - Words and phrases: Cumshaw, 1931-1976 (Offsite-box 2715, Folder 5)
  - Words and phrases: Da-Dz, 1935-1993 (Offsite-box 2715, Folder 6-18)
  - Words and phrases: Days and hours, 1944-1945 (Offsite-box 2715, Folder 19)
  - Words and phrases: Democracy, 1949-1975 (Offsite-box 2715, Folder 20)
  - Words and phrases: Democrat Party, 1956-1976 (Offsite-box 2715, Folder 21)
  - Words and phrases: Depression, 1953-1982 (Offsite-box 2715, Folder 22)
  - Words and phrases: Detente, 1968-1984 (Offsite-box 2715, Folder 23)
  - Words and phrases: Ea-El, 1929-1993 (Offsite-box 2715, Folder 24-25)
  - Words and phrases: Empi-Ez, 1938-1992 (Offsite-box 2716, Folder 1-15)
  - Words and phrases: Egghead, 1955-1983 (Offsite-box 2716, Folder 16)
  - Words and phrases: Establishment, 1965-1982 (Offsite-box 2716, Folder 17)
  - Words and phrases: Ethnic designations, 1968-1993 (Offsite-box 2716, Folder 18-27)
  - Words and phrases: Ethnic purity, 1976 (Offsite-box 2716, Folder 28)
  - Words and phrases: Euphemism, 1969-1993 (Offsite-box 2717, Folder 1-2)
  - Words and phrases: Exaggeration, 1967 (Offsite-box 2717, Folder 3)
  - Words and phrases: Faa-Ft, 1934-1993 (Offsite-box 2717, Folder 4-26)
  - Words and phrases: Fua-Fz, 1943-1993 (Offsite-box 2718, Folder 1-2)
  - Words and phrases: Finalize, 1958-1961 (Offsite-box 2718, Folder 3)
  - Words and phrases: Foreign, 1963-1991 (Offsite-box 2718, Folder 4-6)
  - Words and phrases: Fuck, 1969-1980 (Offsite-box 2718, Folder 7)
  - Words and phrases: Ga-Grn, 1929-1993 (Offsite-box 2718, Folder 8-20)
  - Words and phrases: Gro-Gz, 1932-1992 (Offsite-box 2739, Folder 1-3)
  - Words and phrases: G.I., 1945-1962 (Offsite-box 2739, Folder 4)
  - Words and phrases: Gobbledygook, 1944-1988 (Offsite-box 2739, Folder 5-10)
  - Words and phrases: Great Society, 1955-1964 (Offsite-box 2739, Folder 11)
  - Words and phrases: Haa-Hoz, 1934-1993 (Offsite-box 2739, Folder 12-25)
  - Words and phrases: Hp-Hz, 1938-1993 (Offsite-box 2740, Folder 1)
  - Words and phrases: Hamburger, 1953-1981 (Offsite-box 2740, Folder 2)
  - Words and phrases: Homonyms, 1985 (Offsite-box 2740, Folder 3)
  - Words and phrases: Hot dog, 1934-1972 (Offsite-box 2740, Folder 4)
  - Words and phrases: Ia-Iz, 1931-1993 (Offsite-box 2740, Folder 5-12)
  - Words and phrases: Jaa-Jz, 1934-1992 (Offsite-box 2740, Folder 13-17)
  - Words and phrases: Ka-Kh, 1946-1993 (Offsite-box 2740, Folder 18-20)
  - Words and phrases: Ki-Kz, 1936-1993 (Offsite-box 2741, Folder 1-6)
  - Words and phrases: Kilroy Was Here, 1946-1966 (Offsite-box 2741, Folder 7)
  - Words and phrases: Laa-Lz, 1934-1993 (Offsite-box 2741, Folder 8-19)
  - Words and phrases: Law and Order, 1968-1970 (Offsite-box 2741, Folder 20)
  - Words and phrases: Liberal, 1938-1992 (Offsite-box 2741, Folder 21)
  - Words and phrases: Linkage, 1969-1983 (Offsite-box 2741, Folder 22)
  - Words and phrases: Long, 1931-1991 (Offsite-box 2741, Folder 23)
  - Words and phrases: Maa-Mam, 1931-1992 (Offsite-box 2741, Folder 24-25)
  - Words and phrases: Man-Mor, 1936-1993 (Offsite-box 2742, Folder 1-25)
  - Words and phrases: Mos-Mz, 1951-1993 (Offsite-box 2743, Folder 1-5)
  - Words and phrases: McCarthyism, 1951-1965 (Offsite-box 2743, Folder 6)
  - Words and phrases: Metaphors and similes, 1944-1993 (Offsite-box 2743, Folder 7)
  - Words and phrases: Mod, 1964-1966 (Offsite-box 2743, Folder 8)
  - Words and phrases: Moderation, 1955-1956 (Offsite-box 2743, Folder 9)
  - Words and phrases: Mon Oncle, 1960-1964 (Offsite-box 2743, Folder 10)
  - Words and phrases: Moonlighting, 1957-1964 (Offsite-box 2743, Folder 11)
  - Words and phrases: Motherfucker, 1965-1969 (Offsite-box 2743, Folder 12)
  - Words and phrases: Musharawah, 1964-1969 (Offsite-box 2743, Folder 13)
  - Words and phrases: Na-Nz, 1934-1993 (Offsite-box 2743, Folder 14-24)
  - Words and phrases: Negro, 1942-1987 (Offsite-box 2743, Folder 25)
    This folder contains materials relating to the history and use of the word.
  - Words and phrases: New Deal, 1938-1982 (Offsite-box 2744, Folder 1)
  - Words and phrases: New Frontier, 1960-1967 (Offsite-box 2744, Folder 2)
  - Words and phrases: New words and phrases, 1931-1992 (Offsite-box 2744, Folder 3-7)
  - Words and phrases: Nigger(s), 1959-1993 (Offsite-box 2744, Folder 8)
  - Words and phrases: Oa-Oz, 1933-1990 (Offsite-box 2744, Folder 9-12)
  - Words and phrases: Obscene, 1965-1993 (Offsite-box 2744, Folder 13-14)
  - Words and phrases: O.K., 1942-1981 (Offsite-box 2744, Folder 15)
  - Words and phrases: "On Language" column, 1989-1993 (Offsite-box 2744, Folder 16-20)
  - Words and phrases: "On Language" column, 1979-1988 (Offsite-box 2745, Folder 1-11)
  - Words and phrases: Origin, 1943-1987 (Offsite-box 2745, Folder 12)
  - Words and phrases: Paa-Ph, 1929-1993 (Offsite-box 2745, Folder 13-20)
  - Words and phrases: Pia-Pz, 1929-1993 (Offsite-box 2746, Folder 1-14)
  - Words and phrases: Peaceful coexistence, 1954-1978 (Offsite-box 2746, Folder 16)
  - Words and phrases: Peace through strength, 1964-1976 (Offsite-box 2746, Folder 15)
  - Words and phrases: Pig(s), 1964-1979 (Offsite-box 2746, Folder 17)
  - Words and phrases: Pizazz, 1957-1969 (Offsite-box 2746, Folder 18)
  - Words and phrases: Posh, 1958-1982 (Offsite-box 2746, Folder 19)
  - Words and phrases: Power to the people, 1970 (Offsite-box 2746, Folder 20)
  - Words and phrases: Prefixes and suffixes, 1956-1991 (Offsite-box 2746, Folder 21)
  - Words and phrases: Publications, 1970-1992 (Offsite-box 2746, Folder 22)
  - Words and phrases: Publish or perish, 1967 (Offsite-box 2748, Folder 1)
  - Words and phrases: Pundit, 1961-1985 (Offsite-box 2748, Folder 2)
  - Words and phrases: Q, 1931-1990 (Offsite-box 2748, Folder 3)
  - Words and phrases: Ra-Rz, 1935-1993 (Offsite-box 2748, Folder 4-10)
  - Words and phrases: Records (superlatives), 1961-1989 (Offsite-box 2748, Folder 11)
  - Words and phrases: Royal, 1951-1957 (Offsite-box 2748, Folder 12)
  - Words and phrases: Saa-Sc, 1932-1993 (Offsite-box 2748, Folder 13-16)
  - Words and phrases: Sd-Soz, 1935-1993 (Offsite-box 2748, Folder 1-18)
  - Words and phrases: Spa-Sz, 1930-1992 (Offsite-box 2777, Folder 1-15)
  - Words and phrases: Serendipity, 1940-1961 (Offsite-box 2777, Folder 16)
  - Words and phrases: Sexist words and phrases, 1972-1993 (Offsite-box 2777, Folder 17-21)
  - Words and phrases: She, 1953-1978 (Offsite-box 2777, Folder 22)
  - Words and phrases: Sock it to 'em, 1968 (Offsite-box 2777, Folder 23)
  - Words and phrases: Sock it to me, 1968 (Offsite-box 2777, Folder 24)
  - Words and phrases: Soft on Communism, 1964 (Offsite-box 2777, Folder 25)
  - Words and phrases: Son of a bitch, 1946-1986 (Offsite-box 2778, Offsite-box 1)
  - Words and phrases: Stagflation, 1970-1989 (Offsite-box 2778, Offsite-box 2)
  - Words and phrases: Statism, 1949-1957 (Offsite-box 2778, Offsite-box 3)
  - Words and phrases: Stonewall, 1957-1974 (Offsite-box 2778, Offsite-box 4)
  - Words and phrases: Ta-Ty, 1930-1993 (Offsite-box 2778, Offsite-box 5-18)
  - Words and phrases: To be, 1969-1992 (Offsite-box 2778, Offsite-box 19)
  - Words and phrases: Togetherness, 1957-1960 (Offsite-box 2778, Offsite-box 20)
  - Words and phrases: Ua-Um, 1947-1990 (Offsite-box 2778, Offsite-box 21)
  - Words and phrases: Un-Uz, 1935-1993 (Offsite-box 2779, Folder 1-3)
  - Words and phrases: Uncle Tom, 1964-1970 (Offsite-box 2779, Folder 4)
  - Words and phrases: United States, 1976-1992 (Offsite-box 2779, Folder 5)
  - Words and phrases: Vaa-Vz, 1943-1992 (Offsite-box 2779, Folder 6-15)
  - Words and phrases: Veep, 1949-1952 (Offsite-box 2779, Folder 16)
  - Words and phrases: Voodoo economics, 1980-1982 (Offsite-box 2779, Folder 17)
  - Words and phrases: Wa-Wil, 1930-1992 (Offsite-box 2779, Folder 18-25)
  - Words and phrases: Wim-Wz, 1938-1992 (Offsite-box 2768, Folder 1-2)
  - Words and phrases: Wimp, 1980-1992 (Offsite-box 2768, Folder 3)
  - Words and phrases: X, 1957-1992 (Offsite-box 2768, Folder 4)
  - Words and phrases: Ya-Yz, 1935-1992 (Offsite-box 2768, Folder 5-9)
  - Words and phrases: Z, 1936-1993 (Offsite-box 2768, Folder 10)